in this short video I'm going to
demonstrate how you can apply some
paragraph for mutton to a letter to
enhance the appearance the example I'm
going to use is a document that
downloaded from the vision allene
website the first thing I need to do is
I'm going to change the line spacing so
that the letter is more evenly spaced
all over the page so once I've
highlighted all of the text I will then
go to the line spacing icon and select
1.5 I could try to but 1.5 looks about
right for this document and the content
so once i've selected that as you can
see that has spread the information out
over the page more evenly
the second task would be to change the
alignment of the business address which
should really be on the right-hand side
so again I will highlight the address go
back up to the paragraph section select
a line rate tool from the bar click on
that and that will then move the address
over to the right the next formatting I
want to apply is to this block of text
here which I think should be bullet
pointed so again I will highlight the
text go back up to the paragraph section
select the bullet icon and from the drop
down select a simple bullet point the
very last piece of formatting that I
will apply to the letter is to add a
border to the pH again go back up to the
paragraph section I will select the
border icon in the drop down beside it
and from the list select borders and
shading once the borders and shading box
has come up I will then select page
border and select a suitable style for
this document I'll go the Selective
double line style I need to check here
to make sure that it's being applied to
the whole document and then select look
here as you can see that now makes the
let that look much more presentable